const stuff = [
  { question: "5 + 6", answer: "11" },
  { question: "6 + 6", answer: "12" },
  { question: "7 + 6", answer: "13" },
  { question: "8 + 6", answer: "14" },
  { question: "9 + 6", answer: "15" },
  { question: "10 + 6", answer: "16" },
  { question: "4 + 7", answer: "11" },
  { question: "5 + 7", answer: "12" },
  { question: "7 + 7", answer: "14" },
  { question: "8 + 7", answer: "15" },
  { question: "9 + 7", answer: "16" },
  { question: "10 + 7", answer: "17" },
  { question: "3 + 8", answer: "11" },
  { question: "4 + 8", answer: "12" },
  { question: "5 + 8", answer: "13" },
  { question: "8 + 8", answer: "16" },
  { question: "9 + 8", answer: "17" },
  { question: "10 + 8", answer: "18" },
  { question: "2 + 9", answer: "11" },
  { question: "3 + 9", answer: "12" },
  { question: "4 + 9", answer: "13" },
  { question: "5 + 9", answer: "14" },
  { question: "10 + 9", answer: "19" },
];

export default stuff;
